<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
 <title>Dirk Jan Buter&#039;s Magazine</title>
 <description>Technology for Personal Growth and Innovation</description>
 <link>https://dirkjanbuter.github.io/magazine/en/</link>
 <copyright>Dirk Jan Buter is the owner of this magazine. If you want to use text, images or anything else from it, please ask me first. Thank you!</copyright>
 <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 09:21:33 CET</pubDate>
 <ttl>1800</ttl>
 <item>
  <title>Healthy resolutions: A new year, a new you</title>
  <description>Personally, 2023 was a year full of changes. It was an educational year and I learned a number of things that I want to use for my new year resolutions.

At a meetup about biohacking I learned that...</description>
  <link>https://dirkjanbuter.github.io/magazine/en/healthy-resolutions-a-new-year-a-new-you.html</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 09:18:13 CET</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>DNA testing kits: Access to genetic information for everyone</title>
  <description>DNA, the building block of our lives, is an amazing molecule that contains unique information about us. *Understanding our DNA can give us valuable insights about our health, hereditary traits and eve...</description>
  <link>https://dirkjanbuter.github.io/magazine/en/dna-testing-kits-access-to-genetic-information-for-everyone.html</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 17:17:52 CET</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Meet ChatGPT, today&#039;s homework robot</title>
  <description>The world of technology is constantly evolving and its impact can be felt in the classroom. The introduction of ChatGPT changes the way students learn. ChatGPT is a conversation-based AI platform that...</description>
  <link>https://dirkjanbuter.github.io/magazine/en/meet-chatgpt-todays-homework-robot.html</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 17:17:52 CET</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>A new look at the world&#039;s current problems</title>
  <description>Improving the world is a big task, but with a small contribution we can make a big difference. *There are many problems in the world that pose us a major challenge.* Just think of climate change, food...</description>
  <link>https://dirkjanbuter.github.io/magazine/en/a-new-look-at-the-worlds-current-problems.html</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 17:17:52 CET</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>How to overcome life&#039;s limits</title>
  <description>We all experience limits in life. Whether it concerns financial, emotional or physical boundaries. *Overcoming those limits often requires determination and a lot of courage*. If you want to get the m...</description>
  <link>https://dirkjanbuter.github.io/magazine/en/how-to-overcome-lifes-limits.html</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 17:17:52 CET</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Living forever: The critical view of cryonics</title>
  <description>What is the truth behind the cryonics prejudices? Because I notice in my environment that people are too quick to judge. Why are they dismissive of it and are these gut feelings correct? In this artic...</description>
  <link>https://dirkjanbuter.github.io/magazine/en/living-forever-the-critical-view-of-cryonics.html</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 17:17:53 CET</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>How do I make good images of the microcosm?</title>
  <description>In the invisible world, where the human eye is inadequate, the microscope is the indispensable tool for the biohacker. An instrument that opens doors to small miracles. Through craftsmanship with a mi...</description>
  <link>https://dirkjanbuter.github.io/magazine/en/how-do-i-make-good-images-of-the-microcosm.html</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 17:17:53 CET</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Welcome and open a new world and discover its secrets!</title>
  <description>My interest in the world and technology led me to start this magazine. My name is Dirk Jan Buter, and *I have been dreaming of a different and better world all my life.* I don’t take everything for...</description>
  <link>https://dirkjanbuter.github.io/magazine/en/welcome-and-open-a-new-world-and-discover-its-secrets.html</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 17:17:53 CET</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>David Ishee&#039;s incredible journey from Mississippi to the world</title>
  <description>David Ishee is a dog breeder originally from Mississippi who first came into the spotlight in 2016 when he decided to biohack Mastiff puppies to make them glow in the dark. *In 2019, he was one of the...</description>
  <link>https://dirkjanbuter.github.io/magazine/en/david-ishees-incredible-journey-from-mississippi-to-the-world.html</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 17:17:53 CET</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Improving the lives of people with disabilities</title>
  <description>Dicky, my great-aunt I was named after (my nickname is Dick), was confined to a wheelchair most of her life. At the age of 18, she was diagnosed with polio. As a child, we, together with my parents, v...</description>
  <link>https://dirkjanbuter.github.io/magazine/en/improving-the-lives-of-people-with-disabilities.html</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 17:17:53 CET</pubDate>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Forget the coconuts: Choose your world or build your own paradise</title>
  <description>I signed up for cryonics, a procedure that freezes people just after they die. People undergoing this procedure hope that science will reach the point where they can later be brought back to life and...</description>
  <link>https://dirkjanbuter.github.io/magazine/en/forget-the-coconuts-choose-your-world-or-build-your-own-paradise.html</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 17:17:52 CET</pubDate>
 </item>
</channel>
</rss>
